No!
不要
I'm going to die!
會死的
I can't take it!
不受不了
No, don't put it in!
不 不要再灌進去了
We can't take this!
你不能對我們這樣
You sick bastard!
你這個變態的混蛋
No, stop that you fucking asshole!
停手你他媽的混蛋
No, it's cold!
不要 好冷啊
No, stop!
不要住手
Stop torturing me!
住手
No, stop right now!
不要快住手
Akemi, no!
明美不要
No, please stop!
不行 快不行了
No, don't come inside me!
不要 不要射在裡面
Not inside!
不要射在裡面
Isaku is deranged!
遺作是瘋子
If we keep doing this...
如果我們繼續這樣下去…
every single one of us will go insane.
我們一樣會變得瘋狂的
But...
但是…
I'll keep him distracted.
我去轉移他的注意力
Find Kenta for us.
你快去找健太
Please!
求求你
Kenta!
健太
He'll know I've been raped.
他已經知道我被強姦了
That's not fair!
怎麼可能
Isaku Respect
遺作 ～Respect～
Third Episode: The end of debauchery
第三幕 快樂的結果
Sacrifice
Part A 犧牲
You deserve this.
這是你應得的
What?
什麼
You were always...
你總是…
so popular at school.
在學校裡這麼受歡迎
I was sick of your fake, virginal act.
我討厭你虛假的行為
Stop it!
不要這樣
Now, you're another slutty whore!
現在你又是一個低賤的玩物了
Look at your tits.
看看你的奶頭
They're fucking huge.
真的太大了
Like a cow.
就像乳牛一樣
Don't!
不要
Stop no!
不要 不要啊
Moo, like a cow.
就像乳牛一樣
Say moo.
說吧
Moo.
不要
Please Miyuki, stop it right now.
求求你 美由紀 不要
Just go away!
不要這樣啊
I know you like it.
我知道你喜歡它
I'd bet your pussy's wet with excitement!
我敢打賭你的下陰已經濕得一塌糊塗了
Don't touch me!
不要
These tits are the only features that make you special.
你最特別的就是這雙淫乳了
Yes!
是吧
Kotomi, you have soft tits!
琴未那柔軟的雙乳
It feels great!
感覺真棒啊
Rika!
裡香
Kenta!
健太
Isaku, after you do whatever you want to Miyuki...
遺作以後你想怎麼玩弄美由紀都可以了
You'll let everyone see home again?
你可以讓大家回家嗎
No, Rika, this man's crazy!
不要 裡香 他是個瘋子
Sorry Miyuki!
對不起 美由紀
We don't have any other choice.
我們沒有其他的選擇
Don't hurt me, I swear, I'll do what you want!
不要傷害我我發誓我會盡力滿足你的
I'll follow your orders!
我會按照你想的去做
I'll behave from now on!
從現在開始
Kenta's here!
健太
Here!
這裡
Good!
好
Whoa!
呀
You pervert!
真討厭
You're just a piece of shit!
你這變態
No!
不要
It's too big!
太大了
Stop!
快住手
Wow!
哇
Look, look!
你看 你看
Stop it!
對了
Don't look!
不要看了
But if you let me know ahead of time...
不過你如果提前告訴我的話…
I won't wear panties.
我會不穿內褲的
Gross!
不要
No more!
停止啊
Stop, this hurts too much!
不要啊 很辛苦啊
I want to tell you...
我想告訴你…
what Isaku said to me.
遺作對我說
He said I have nice legs.
我有一雙漂亮的腿
It's still like a little girl...
就像一個小女孩
but it's firm, plump and tempting.
但它卻非常誘人
With legs like mine...
由於我有這樣的腿
men will only want me for one thing.
男孩想到的就只有一件事
All men will just want to use me and fuck me with their hard cock.
所有的人只想和我發生關係
They'll see me as a toy to fuck, not a human being.
他們只當我是一件洩慾工具
No, no!
不 不要
No, spare me!
不 不要這樣
Please, no! Don't do this!
怎麼會這樣 不要 快拔出來
No!
不要
Kenta!
健太
No, don't go too deep!
不要 不要再進去了
It's too much!
這太過分了
No!
不要
This isn't my fault at all.
這不是我的錯
I didn't have a choice.
我沒得選擇
It's hot!
很熱
Pull it out!
不要
It's painful!
我受不了了
This is a man?
這還是一個人嗎
It's tearing me!
裂開了
I can't believe that big thing...
我不能相信這現時…
that ugly thing...
這醜陋的現時…
was just inside me, too!
我也身在其中
Please help me, please!
救救我 求求你
No!
不要
Stop!
不要啊
No, don't you dare!
不要 快停止
Come inside me and I'll fucking kill you, damn it!
你再繼續下去我就殺了你
Don't!
不要
I said don't you dare come inside me.
我已經說了 不要射在我裡面
Kotomi Asakawa
Part B 淺川 琴未
Leave us alone!
放開我們能
Not inside me!
不要灌進來
No, the water's freezing cold!
不要 好冷 好冷啊
Please!
求求你
Pull it out!
拔出來
Don't do it!
不要
Stop, that's not going to fit!
不要這麼做
No, no!
不要 不要
No, not again!
不要 再來
Stop!
停手
Just pull it out!
不要這樣弄
I can't handle this any more!
不要 快要出來了
No, it's too big!
不要 已經夠了
You're hurting me, stop!
我受不了了 快停手
You piece of shit!
要出來了
I'm about to lose my mind!
裡香 那裡不要…
Just stop!
求求你
It's coming!
出來了
God help me!
不要啊
Please, just look away!
不要看 不要看
Kenta!
健太
All of us had...
我們大家都已經…
no hope left inside us anymore.
沒有希望再離開這裡了
Isaku would laugh and say things like...
遺作笑著說
Akemi's boyfriends have taught her well.
明美的男友已經教她
She gives great head.
用胸部弄了
On the other hand...
另一方面…
Rika thinks that sucking cock is like licking candy.
裡香認為口交就像吃糖果
I will, I'll say it!
我會我會說的
We were Isaku's sex slaves!
我們成為了遺作的性奴隸
You taste better than Kenta.
你的比健太的好吃
Your cock is so much bigger!
你的小弟真大啊
I love it.
我最喜歡它了
Your asshole tastes delicious, master!
你的屁眼真好舔啊 主人
It's so much thicker than Kenta's!
比健太的打多了
Yes, it's better than his smelly cock!
是的這是比他的小雞好好多了
Wait!
不要
God, this hurts!
不要 好辛苦啊
I can't even think straight!
我不能繼續下去了
My wet pussy feel like it's melting!
我我陰道快融化了
I can't!
不行了
Akemi!
明美
No more!
不要這樣
No!
不要
Don't hurt me anymore!
求求你 不要
Let me go!
放過我吧
Stop!
不要
No, no!
不要不要
He would rarely rest.
他很少休息
We were subjected to endless torture.
我們遭受無休止的折磨
Suddenly...
突然…
The day came when the hideous fiend was gone, forever.
有一天可怕的惡魔終於永遠離開了
His ugly face...
他的醜惡嘴臉…
was smiling.
在微笑
I'm dreaming about that.
我是在做夢嗎
This incident...
這件事…
was never made public, especially since Isaku...
從來沒有對外公開特別是因為遺作 …
wasn't alive to be prosecuted.
是不是還活著可能遭受起訴
That experience left...
那件事情後…
a deep scar in all of us.
所有的人都留下了永不磨滅的傷痕
You're going to sit out again?
你要坐下了嗎
I don't want...
我不想…
anybody looking at my body.
任何人看到我的身體
Stop!
笨蛋 你不是正穿運動褲嗎
Stop acting like a kid!
真想個小孩子
Leave me alone.
不要管我
I don't want to be like you.
我不想成為像您一樣的
Hey, stop that!
你這蠢材
I don't want to pretend I'm a grown-up.
我不想假裝我是一個大人
Everyone's trying so hard to move on.
每個人都嘗試繼續往前走
Can I give you an advice?
我可以給你一個建議
In order to...
為了…
move on, you need to accept the past.
繼續往前走你必須接受過去
You can't just erase your memory.
你不能抹去你的記憶
It will eat you alive inside.
不然它會把你吞噬
Come on, Miyuki!
來吧美由紀
It's important to dream, and take action to achieve what you want!
你要採取行動實現你的夢想啊
Hold it, Kotomi!
等等琴未
Go tell Kenta how you feel.
去告訴健太你的感受
You should have plenty of time.
你應該有足夠的時間
All right?
好吧
You really are a sweet girl.
你真的是一個可愛的姑娘
You might regret being so nice later.
我相信你以後會更好的